[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday", "April", "April"], "LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "What's happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Well, I think you just jinxed it, Piers, because unfortunately the weather is set to change and there are predictions we will have a few showers on Friday, but it's April and Britain is known for having April showers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "How does it feeling to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "I mean it is tangible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Is this true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "ICHOLL: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "What have we heard about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Well, it's true that not everyone wishes the happy couple, you know, a very peaceful day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "What kind of preparations has there been security wise for this event?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Well, obviously there's been a massive security operation in London and good security is invisible security.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "I've played them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Why is this such a huge event do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, I think this is Britain at its greatest, at its best.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Did you ever meet Diana?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "And what was she like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "She was really normal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "I mean they're kind of looking around saying, all this countries want to know about our -- you know, our royal wedding and think it's a huge thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "And America in particular is going crazy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "What do you think of Kate Middleton?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "I think Kate -- I've never met her, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate Middleton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Can you even begin to imagine what it's like at the level that Kate Middleton is about to face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "I can't even imagine.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate Middleton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 235, "question": "What advice would you give to the royal couple about marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Well, I think --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "You've (INAUDIBLE) it out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "I have definitely cracked it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "When you come back to London, what do you feel when you come back and it's all exciting like this and there's this huge event?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I get so proud.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Are you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Diana"], "PERSON": ["Emanuels"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "The dress?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, I don't think she's going to go for the huge big poofy thing that the Emanuels did for Diana.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Jewelry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "I think she will wear some of the Queen's jewelry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "And do what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Well, have the tiara and something floral in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Just delicately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "What do you imagine he might want to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "EYMOUR: Gosh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Were you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Do you believe in the monarchy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "I believe in the monarchy when it's done properly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "And where will you be on big day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "I'll be right here, right next to you actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "I mean it will be exciting, won't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "It's going to be so exciting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 439, "question": "How are you feeling about me being here with Anderson Cooper, Cat Deeley and Richard Quest, the royal wedding A-team?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "They are the royal --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson Cooper", "Deeley", "Richard Quest"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "You panicking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "And this is almost like our little club here, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Elizabeth, this must bring back so many memories for you, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "It really does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Have you any idea who has designed this dress?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Absolutely no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Is that the kind of feeling you're getting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Well, I'm sure it's not going to look anything like Diana's dress because that was really such an '80s kind of a look.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "But I'm sure there'll be some fashion twists, something unexpected, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "EX", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Jane was surmising it may be a combination of tiara and flowers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "When you designed Diana's dress -- obviously, it was one of the world's most legendary dresses -- what kind of pressure did you feel as that designer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Well, David and I at the time, we'd just left college, really, been out about a year.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Why did Diana choose you, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "I think she just liked us.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Was Diana under -- I mean, obviously under huge pressure at the time, but did she show it to you when you were having all the fittings and stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "No, she never seemed to be under pressure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Is that the most pressurized moment for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "I think it's the whole build-up, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Would you have liked to have made Kate's dress, or is once in a lifetime enough for this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Oh, I think I would have loved to have done it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "I mean, what will happen to the designer of Kate Middleton's dress, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Well, first of all, you're going to see millions of copies of the dress everywhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate Middleton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Do you know how many brides got married in similar dresses to Diana's?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Oh, there must be lots and lots.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Are you excited about the wedding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "What would she have made of Kate Middleton, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Oh, I'm sure she would have really liked her.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate Middleton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dave"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "If it gets snagged on the way out, do you have a spare dress?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "MANUEL: Well, I don't know if that happened in the past, but Dave and I decided we would have a back-up and just in case anybody worked out what it was going to look like, we made another dress, different design, and it was hanging there all ready to go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "And yet nobody has a clue what it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "NN", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "What did she say to you when she got a chance to talk to you again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Well, you know, after we got back to the studio and we were feeling a little bit deflated -- it had been such an amazing day, and it was all quiet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dave"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Did you stay in touch with her over the years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Well, we did, but then, you know, Dave and I split and we didn't have the business anymore.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "Could you sleep the night before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Did anything go wrong on the day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "Nothing went wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "I mean, can you put a figure on what this might be worth to a designer in the modern day now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Oh, I would imagine, you know, if it's all handled properly, a lot of money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "And if you were a betting woman -- are you a betting woman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Burton"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "If you were, given all the speculation about all the designers -- you know all these people -- who would you have your money on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "Well, everybody says it's Sarah Burton (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "What was it like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "It was absolutely fantastic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "... were they resolutely normal?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "Absolutely normal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "Prince William -- what did he like and didn't like as a boy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "Oh, traditional favorites, roast chicken, crispy roast potatoes, sausages and mash, and all the traditional English puddings.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Milk chocolate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "I think probably the milk chocolate ones he enjoyed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Do you stay in touch with the royal family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "No, not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 726, "question": "Do you think he'll be cracking the whip with his son, saying, Right, it's got to be healthy organic food?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 727, "answer": "I'm sure William follows in his footsteps, and I'm sure he's very keen on that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "Is there any evidence he can cook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "When he was younger, when he was a little boy, he enjoyed it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "And did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "What did you teach him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "Oh, some chicken dishes and a couple of sweet things, as well, I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 742, "question": "Is he that kind of guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 743, "answer": "Possibly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "That's one of the things he enjoys.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "Is that his, like, royal signature dish?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "IN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "It could be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "What was it -- when you were working for the royal family, is it a strange experience compared to a normal job, I mean, or would you get very quickly used to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "OBB: I think it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "Can they be normal, the royals?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "I think they were as normal as it was possible for them to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Did you feel huge pressure when you prepared food?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "Initially, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 774, "question": "What was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 775, "answer": "The details of it -- it was all such a terrifying experience, I can't remember the details.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "Had it all been eaten?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "It had.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "What kind of lady was she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "She was absolutely incredible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 795, "question": "What did you ask her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 796, "answer": "She was wonderful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 799, "question": "Did you ever cook at the palace?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 800, "answer": "Yes, on a few occasions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Kensington Palace"], "LOCATION": ["Highgrove"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "Is it intimidating to be in there and have to prepare meals?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "It was, yes, because our environment was very homely and quite intimate, the kitchens we had at Kensington Palace and Highgrove.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 819, "question": "What are you doing on Friday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 820, "answer": "I'll be at home with my family.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Africa"]}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 830, "question": "What is The Royal Touch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 831, "answer": "Well, I'm working on a book at the moment, which is a food memoir, which is really my journey through the years and my food experiences growing up in South Africa.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 849, "question": "Like his lamb, William did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 850, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 864, "question": "And you can't really go wrong with that, can you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 865, "answer": "No, exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110425pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 866, "question": "And presumably, if she wants to, she can call you for some advice, can she, Kate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 867, "answer": "Anytime.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}}]